reframeit.com 2008-12-10

# Reframe It › Privacy

## User Privacy

Reframe It was built with the purpose of allowing anyone to express their ideas alongside the public web. Our goals is to make Reframe It a secure, transparent and safe space to share information, create an online identity and talk about the public web.

Reframe It cares about the privacy of our users and only uses information members contribute through comments and profiles in ways that are consistent with our company's principles and this privacy policy. Our privacy policy is here to make sure you understand what information we collect and how we use it to improve our user experience. This policy applies to all services on reframeit.com and information collected in the Reframe It margin.

## The information we collect

#### Your Profile

The information that Reframe It asks for during the sign-up process and for user profiles is intended to allow other members of the community to identify you on Reframe It. You can choose whether-or-not to contribute information but, because Reframe It is a community built on sharing ideas, we encourage members to add to their profile to take full advantages of all our services.

Reframe It believes comments and profiles are for the community of users to read and enjoy. Any individual can use Reframe It to post their thoughts and opinions knowing that private information will not be distributed to any third party in a personally identifiable manner. We will not distribute your contact details to third parties and you will not be contacted by third parties on behalf of Reframe It.

#### Browsing Information

When you use the margin on a website a request to our servers is logged so we can deliver comments on the page. We keep your browsing history tied to your profile on our servers for 48 hours to protect our users and guard against violations of our Terms of Service. After 48 hours we scrub this information so your browsing history is not connected to your profile information in a way that is personally identifiable. We keep information on the community browsing in aggregated, anonymized form to allow us to better understand our users.

All public comments are available for the community and can be accessed by any member. This means the information created in comments (private comments excluded) is publicly available.

Once comments are posted, Reframe It will not remove them from the system and we do not practice any form of censorship of ideas, opinions or limit commenting on any particular website. The only exceptions to this policy are (1) where legally required by injunction (2) to enforce the Reframe It Terms of Service (3) to maintain system stability and performance (4) to protect our users and the public's safety.

Reframe It does ask our users to obey the laws of their country, state or province when using our service and endeavor to comment in a civil manner.

All public comments are searchable and sortable by any Reframe It user and linked with the account they were posted from. Reframe It does not take the information you provide in comments and distribute them with personal information to any website to which they refer.

## How We Use the Information We Collect

It is important to us that you understand how we use the information we collect to create a better system for our users. We remove (or scrub) personally identifiable information from the list of pages you request comments for with the Reframe It wxtension. We keep only aggregated metrics about visited webpages that do not contain personally identifiable information. This aggregated information helps us understand where and how the community is using the Reframe It margin. With this information we can recommend users new content and better understand what new features will be of the highest value to the community.

#### Third Parties

Your personal information will never be given out or used to contact you personally about third party offers. If third parties contact us about offers that we believe our users might enjoy we will distribute them through our website or software, but never through independent contacting. You will always have the option to decline offers.

No private information you submit over Reframe It will be distributed to any third party in a way where you will be individually identified. By private information we mean your name, email address, and any other information that can specifically identify you. Reframe it may distribute information to third parties drawn from your comments and profile but will not do so in a way where you are identified by your private information. Reframe It uses the comments and profiles of users to gather information on the Reframe It Community. We do this to better understand our users, to improve the system, and offer our users better, more relevant services.

Reframe It may offer partner services or features from third parties through our website or by email which we feel would be useful to our users. These will be offered on an optional basis and users can choose not to receive such emails if and when such emails are sent out. Reframe It will also send service related emails and updates about the Reframe It community to our users.

Sometimes Reframe It offers special account features to specific classes of users who benefit from promotional services. These users' accounts allow the display of information about themselves or their company they represent in their profiles and comments they post. Because the holders of these accounts desire Reframe It to make the public aware of their presence on our service, Reframe It does release names, titles and other information about these users to third parties for promotional purposes. We will not release the personal contact information of these users to third parties. These special user classes include all special promotional projects and Noted Authorities.

The exceptions Reframe It makes to releasing personal information to other parties are (1) where legally required by subpoena or warrant (2) to enforce the Reframe It Terms of Service (3) to maintain system stability and performance (4) to protect our users and the public's safety.

#### Controlling your Information

Reframe It does allow users to find their friends' accounts using exact e-mail address searches. This functionality helps you quickly find members of the Reframe It community you already have contact information for. A user must already know your exact email address to find your account. This service is by default active for all members but can be deactivated in your user profile page.

#### Secure Accounts

We strive to provide our users security for their accounts and take all reasonable steps to prevent unauthorized access and disclosure of their personal information. Access to your information is limited within the Reframe It staff to employees providing direct support services and always on a limited basis.

#### Cookies

Reframe It utilizes cookies to store preferences and information on users' website sessions. This is used to improve the functionality of reframeit.com. We use cookies to synchronize the Reframe It extension with websites and send users' account names in this information. These are the same account names that freely appear in your user profile and are displayed on comments. Information stored in cookies is never personally identifiable and users have the option of disabling cookies through their web browser. Be aware that disabling or limiting the permission of cookies will affect your experience on reframeit.com and may disable the extension.

## Links

All links to websites other than reframeit.com are the sole responsibility of their originators and Reframe It does not take responsibility for the privacy policies or company policies of these web sites. When providing information to reframeit.com check the URL box at the top of your web browser to ensure it does actually read "reframeit.com" in the URL address.

Reframe it does allow the creation of groups with limited access to membership and comments and allows group administrators/moderators to control the admissions process. Reframe It will take all reasonable steps to maintain the integrity of these groups, but be aware that the information posted in private/restricted groups is only as secure as the membership policy of your group administrators. Group administrators may be offered the ability to reuse comments posted by members of a group in another context.

## Revisions to This Policy

By using Reframe It you consent to the terms expressed in this policy. Reframe It reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time and will take reasonable steps to make users aware of these changes.
